{
    "subject": "resource/OrangeScape",
    "predicate": "ontology/product",
    "object": "resource/Kissflow",
    "human_readable": "OrangeScape is a product called Kissflow.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9798778891563416,
            "question": "Is Kissflow a product created by OrangeScape?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8710002899169922,
            "question": "Are there any other products developed by OrangeScape besides Kissflow?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7263728380203247,
            "question": "What is Kissflow known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.726239025592804,
            "question": "What is the name of the product developed by OrangeScape?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6162640452384949,
            "question": "What type of company is OrangeScape?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39980432391166687,
            "question": "What are the key features of Kissflow?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3057636022567749,
            "question": "Who are the target users of Kissflow?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2869564890861511,
            "question": "Can you provide more information about Kissflow?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24855534732341766,
            "question": "How does Kissflow benefit its users?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20714153349399567,
            "question": "Does OrangeScape develop software solutions?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=OrangeScape is a product called Kissflow.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7099_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does Kissflow benefit its users?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7099_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide more information about Kissflow?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7099_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are the target users of Kissflow?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7099_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7099_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7099_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7099_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7099_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7099_127.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7099_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7099_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7099_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7099_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7099_52.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention OrangeScape as the company behind the software platform KiSSFLOW, and also refer to KiSSFLOW as a product of OrangeScape. This suggests that OrangeScape is indeed a product called Kissflow."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Kissflow was previously known as Orangescape and that Kissflow offers its suite of products globally. This supports the statement that OrangeScape is a product called Kissflow."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "OrangeScape is a software platform company and KiSSFLOW is one of its SaaS products.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Kissflow is a product suite offered by OrangeScape.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information consistently refers to OrangeScape as a company name and Kissflow as a product or platform developed by OrangeScape, indicating that OrangeScape and Kissflow are distinct entities.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Kissflow is the brand name of the company that was originally founded as Orangescape. The company changed its US company name to Kissflow Inc. in 2019 as part of a brand consolidation exercise, while retaining \"KiSSFLOW\" as the product name for its suite of business process and workflow automation tools.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}